Our school uniform...
Were you cursed by the cat statue?
Damn!
He's quick!
How did she find out about the curse?!
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru...
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
〈（潤平）ウチの制服？〉
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
（朱莉）猫地蔵にでも呪われた？
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
失礼ッ
速ッ
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
〈何で　呪いのことを！？〉
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari de
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai!
might prove to be a big opportunity!
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo mukeru yo
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyanderful
It's really a wonderful cat power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 06!
Milk & Bitter & Spice & Sugar
Someone found out about it?
（ニャムサス）バレただって？
We told you to keep it a secret!
（タマ）気づかれちゃダメって
言ったじゃないですかい→
Misfortune will befall both you and that girl!
ダンナにも　その娘にも
災いが降りかかるんですぜい
I wonder if she'll be all right.
（ニャムサス）その娘　ダイジョブかね
明日　話をしてみます
I'll talk to her tomorrow.
（凪）オープン
≪ワン　ワン
I'll go buy some bread.
ちょっと　パン買ってくるね
What's the matter with Kaede?
どうしたんだ　楓は
She's been like that since we went to the amusement park.
（加奈子）この前
遊園地　行ってからっすよ
ほお～
Yeah?
Are you plotting something again?
また何か　企んでませんか？
Stop blaming me for everything.
人聞きの悪いことを
言わないでくれたまえ
I didn't expect that Junpei-kun would be interested in any girl besides Mizuno.
≪（晴彦）潤平君が　水野以外の
女子に興味を持つとは…
（晃太）今度は
後輩ツインテール狙いなのか？
He's after a twin-tailed kouhai now?
I really love twin-tails myself.
（晴彦）俺は　ツインテール
大好物ですけどねえ
Yeah?
へえ～
ドッキンコ！
Haruhiko!
It's not that I'm curious or anything,
これっぽっちも　気にならないが
今の話　詳しく聞こうか　んッ！
but tell me what you were just talking about.
ハッハッハッ
加奈子　ダメだよ
Kanako, don't do that.
こういうときは
優しく聞くものだ
In situations like this, you need to ask gently.
Now...
さあ　教えてくれるよね
you'll tell us, won't you?
Yes, happy to.
はい　喜んで
I couldn't learn her name even after asking Haruhiko.
〈晴彦に聞いても　わからなかった〉
There are so many girls with twin-tails.
〈ツインテールなんか
たくさん　いるし〉
It's not gonna be easy to find her.
〈そう簡単には　見つかんねえか〉
U-Um...
（琴音）あ　あの…
高坂先輩　これ　読んでください
Kousaka-senpai, would you read this?
I found her in no time flat!
〈速攻で　見つかったーッ〉
…て　これ？
Wait, is this...
A letter?
To Mr. Junpei Kousaka
手紙…　そうだ
昨日の話で　聞きたいことが
Oh hey, I want to ask you something about yesterday—
She's gone!
…て　いない
何なんだ
What the heck?
Kirishima... Kotone?
桐島　琴音？
It must be a challenge or something.
どうせ　また　果たし状とか…
I'm always looking at you.
（琴音）「先輩のこと
いつも見ていました」
I really love you.
「先輩のことが好きです」
If it suits you, please let me be your date.
「もし　よかったら
つきあってください」
ほッ　本物！？
It's the real thing?!
This is a mistake!
これは　間違いよ
アンタなんか　大ッ嫌い！　フンッ
I hate you!
〈コクられて　フラれた～
何これ！？〉
I received a confession and then got dumped!
What the heck?!
ちょッ　待った
Wait a sec!
I-I...
はッ…　話がある
I need to talk to you.
何で　あのことを…
How do you know—
I need to talk to you too.
アタシも　話があるわ
放課後　お寺に来て
Come to the temple after school, Kousaka-senpai.
高坂先輩
When there's trouble between a boy and a girl, the boy should always concede.
≪（先生）異性とトラブったら　男から
折れろ　ここは試験に出すから…
This will be on the finals, so take...
That girl...
〈昨日の…〉
〈どういう関係なんだろう〉
What's his relationship with her?
And what's this "curse of the cat statue"?
〈猫地蔵の呪いって　何なのかなあ〉
〈何で　にらまれてるんだろう　俺〉
Why are they all glaring at me?
So anyway, I'm here.
〈言われるがまま　来てみたが〉
Hey, Master!
ああ　ダンナ～
Did you make any progress?
進展は　あったのかい？
No.
ああ　いや
≪（ノワール）ふ～ん→
I guess he really can understand what we're saying.
本当に
アタシ達の言葉が　わかるようね
Noir!
（タマ）ノワール！
知り合いか？
You know her?
（タマ）同じ釜のキャットフードを
食べた仲でさあ
We once lived under the same roof.
Your dear Nyam nee-san's master is very plain.
品のない顔ね　アンタの慕ってる
ニャムねえさんの　ご主人は
（タマ）ノワール！
Noir!
You're as stuck up as ever.
（ニャムサス）相変わらずな小娘だねえ
I never thought anyone would ever fall prey to the curse.
本当に　呪いにかかる人が
いるなんてね
わ～ッ　いつの間に？
When did you get here?!
How do you know about... you know...
お前　何で知ってんだ？
その…
呪いのこと？
About the curse?
〈うわッ　ハッキリ言っちゃった〉
She said it out loud!
見えるの　アタシは人より
霊感が強い体質だから
I can see it.
I'm more spiritually sensitive than others.
I could spread the news and hasten the effect of the curse.
言いふらして　呪いの進行を
早めてあげてもいいけど
アンタの答えによっては
考え直してあげる
Whether I'll reconsider depends on your reply.
答え？
My reply?
Never get close to Kotone-chan ever again.
これ以上
琴音ちゃんに　近づかないで
とぼけないで
ラブレター　もらったでしょ！
Don't play dumb with me!
She sent you a love letter!
はあ？
お前が　よこしたんだろ！
Huh?! You're the one who gave it to me!
And this!
それに　これ！
（琴音）「○月×日
運命の人を見つけた」
X month, Y day: I found the man of my destiny.
「○月×日　あの人の
不遇っぷりが　たまらない　最高」
X month, Y day: I really love his misfortunes. He's the best.
X month, Y day: I learned his name, blood type, and birthday.
「○月×日
名前と血液型と誕生日　ゲット」
「高坂先輩　好き好き…　ふじこ」
I really, really, really, really love Kousaka-senpai.
I love himwdrftgyhujikolp;@:
「○月×日　高坂先輩と
初めて手を　つないだ」
X month, Y day: we held hands for the first time today.
「○月×日　高坂先輩が強引に…
これ以上は　書けない」
X month, Y day: Kousaka-senpai forced himself on... I can't write any more than that!
S-S-S-She's fantasizing!
で　で　で…　電波系
愛し合ってんじゃない！
何　言ってんだ　お前！？
You do love her!
What did you say?!
You love her!
好きなの？
俺が好きなのは　水…
The girl I love is Miz—
Stare...
何でもない
あくまで　シラを切りとおすのね
Never mind.
Playing dumb, are you?
ニャン　おにゃッ
知ってるのよ　アンタの弱点
I know your weak point.
ツインテール萌えな　アホっぽい先輩が
洗いざらい　しゃべってくれたわ
That brainless guy with the twin-tail fetish told me everything.
〈晴彦～ッ！〉
Haruhiko!
W-Wait! Calm down!
待て　まあ　落ち着け
話し合おう　話を！
Let's talk first!
Let's talk!
問答無用～ッ！
No excuses!
たあーーーッ！
ダンナなら
受け止めてくれると信じてたのに
I was sure you'd catch me, Master.
無理　無理　無理
くっそ～　ムチャクチャな女だ
No, I wouldn't!
Damn, that girl is crazy!
This is like a quarrel between children.
まるで
ガキのケンカだねえ
（朱莉）もう一度　言うわよ
Let me say it again.
琴音ちゃんに　近づかないで
Never get close to Kotone-chan ever again.
だ～から　お前と
つきあってなんか　いねえって
Like I said, I'm not dating you!
はあ？　何　言ってんの…
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Dumb ass!
バカーーーッ！
俺！？
わあーッ！
Another Kirishima Kotone?!
桐島　琴音が
もう１人！？
Are you okay, Kousaka-senpai?
大丈夫ですか　高坂先輩？
ひどいじゃない
朱莉ちゃん
This is mean, Akari-chan.
琴音ちゃん　これは…
Kotone-chan, it's just...
好きになった人が
I thought it strange that every boy I loved withdrew unexpectedly.
いつも　不自然に離れていくから
ヘンだと思ってた
今までも　こんなこと　してたのね
You must've done this in the past too.
She must be the fantasizer who gave me the letter.
〈こっちが　手紙をくれた電波系〉
アタシは
琴音ちゃんのことを思って
I just wanted to protect you, Kotone-chan.
And this is the supernatural girl.
〈こっちが　霊感女〉
Ah ha! They're twins!
そうか　双子か！
していいことと
悪いことが　あるでしょ！
This time you've crossed the line!
お　お　おい…
H-Hey...
Because Dad and Mom got divorced,
だって
お父さんと　お母さんが離婚して
タマとも離れ離れになって
and we had to part with Tama too,
琴音ちゃんまで
離れていっちゃうの
I didn't want to lose you, Kotone-chan!
イヤだったんだもん！
（タマ・ノワール）ご主人…
Master...
So she was desperate not to lose her sister.
〈姉を　とられまいと
必死だったわけか〉
〈つーか　俺って
ただの被害者じゃ？〉
That makes me just collateral damage.
Forget it!
もう　知らない！
おいッ
H-Hey!
ちょっと　待てって
呪いの話が　まだ
Wait up!
We haven't talked about the curse yet!
はあ？
アンタ　空気　読めないの？→
Huh?! Can't you see the situation?!
バカ…
Idio—
Misfortune will befall both you and that girl!
《≪（タマ）ダンナにも　その娘にも
災いが降りかかるんですぜい》
〈呪い…〉
The curse...
〈俺のせいで〉
Because of my sin...
ぜって～　死ぬ　グチャッつったもん
I'm really gonna die.
I heard "splash."
朱莉ちゃん　大丈夫！？
Akari-chan, are you okay?
Akari-chan!
（琴音）朱莉ちゃん
I-I'm sorry...
（朱莉）ごめんなさい
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさ～い！
先輩！
Senpai!
（千鶴）あらあら　潤平君ったら
女の子を　泣かせて
Oh my, Junpei-kun is making a girl cry!
い・け・な・い・ぞ
B-a-d b-o-y.
妄想日記は
しばらく　封印いたします
I'm going to put away my fantasy journal for a while.
アンタは
攻撃対象から　外すわ
I'll take you off my list of targets.
（２人）ご迷惑おかけして
すみませんでした
I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused.
いや～　もう　いいから
Don't worry about it.
アンタ達も
仲よく　おやりよ
You two should get along with each other.
あの子を泣かせたくないだろ？
う～ん
You don't want to make them cry anymore, do you?
タマが　どうしてもっていうのなら
If Tama really begs for it.
Oh dear.
呪いは　ご自身の力で
解かないとなりませんが
You must break the curse on your own, but I'll help you whenever I can.
いつでも　お手伝いはいたします
こッ　琴音ちゃんが言うなら
手伝ってあげても　いいわ
I-If Kotone-chan says so, I can help too.
ああ　ありがとう
Thanks.
〈姉は　いい子だ〉
She's a good girl.
What? You still like him, Kotone-chan?
コトの発端を
忘れてんじゃないわよ！
What do you see in him?!
こんなヤツの　どこがいいのよ～
それは…
It's...
アタシ
不幸体質の方が　大好きなんです
I love men who are plagued with misfortune.
〈姉も　ヤバイ子でした〉
The other sister is highly questionable too.
（琴音）妄想日記は　封印しますが→
I'll put away my fantasy journal, but may I continue to stalk you?
ストーキングは継続させても？
ダメーッ！
No!
（琴音）ねえ　朱莉ちゃん→
See, Akari-chan?
幽体離脱
An out-of-body experience...
宅配便には　出てません
I was not in that "Delivery Service" movie.
（ニャムサス）せっかくの休日なんだから
You have the day off,
ゴロゴロしてないで　依頼のひとつも
片づけてきたら　どうなんだい
so stop being lazy and go make a wish come true.
Coming!
≪（鈴）は～い
ジャマが入らなかったら
If there hadn't been any interference...
…んなわけねえよな
No, never.
≪（鈴）潤平兄ちゃん　お客さんだよ
Junpei-nii-chan, you have visitors.
お客さん？
Visitors?
（鈴）お・ん・な・の・こ
G-i-r-l-s.
水…
Mizu—?!
Hello, Kousaka-senpai.
こんにちは　高坂先輩
（朱莉）あからさまに
イヤそうな顔ね
You look positively annoyed.
奥さん　ご覧になりました？
Oh dear, do you see this?
（母）あんなにカワイイ子が　２人も
Two really cute girls.
隅に　おけませんわねえ
He must be more popular than we thought.
We should celebrate with red bean rice.
今夜は　赤飯にしましょうか
They're total strangers to me. Let's go outside!
知らない人　見てっから…
で　何しに来たんだよ
So, why did you come?
呪いの件に
決まってんじゃない
We came about the curse, of course.
私は別に
どうでも　いいけど
Not that I care, but Kotone-chan insisted on it.
琴音ちゃんが
行くっていうから
それは
わざわざ　どうも
Well, thank you.
So, when were you cursed by the cat statue?
それで　猫地蔵の呪いには
いつ頃　かかったの？
助けた猫の数は？
How many cats have you helped so far?
９月に呪いに　かかって
I was cursed in September, and I think I've helped about twenty so far.
助けたのは　２０匹ぐらいかな
少なッ
１日　１匹　やってれば
That's all?!
You'd have finished in no time if you'd helped one cat a day!
すぐじゃないの
何やってんの！
What have you been doing?!
（ニャムサス）まったくだよ
うっせえな！
Seriously.
Shut up!
俺には　俺の生活があるし
気が乗らないときも　ある！
I have my own life, and sometimes I don't feel like helping!
先輩　猫になって死ぬ気？
Do you want to turn into a cat and die?
…つか　死ねばいいのに
Actually, go ahead and die!
…てか　お前らは平気なのか？
Anyway, are you two okay?
呪いを知った相手にも
災いが起こるって…
I heard the curse hits anyone who learns about it.
アタシ達は　軽い退魔術を使えるから
害は　ないわ
We know basic warding spells, so we don't have a problem.
退魔術？
Warding spells?
だけど　アタシ達には
他人を守るほどの力は　ないの
But we're not powerful enough to help others.
ですから　他の方には　決して
知られないようにしてください
So please be careful, and don't let anyone else learn about this.
まあ
２人に害がないなら　よかったよ
Well, I'm glad that it can't harm you two.
バッ　バッカじゃないの！
D-Don't make fun of me!
早速ですが
ノワールが　いるので
Anyway, because Noir's here, why don't we ask her for a request?
何か　聞いてみては
いかがでしょう？
Settle down.
They're quick to fight even though they used to live together!
（朱莉）一緒に住んでたくせに
すぐケンカする
一緒に住んでた？
They lived together?
ノワールは
アタシ達が引き取りましたが
We kept Noir, but...
タマは　父が引き取ったの
Our father kept Tama.
父？
タマの今の飼い主ってことは…
Your father?
Tama's current owner is...
《（住職）キャバクラ　大好き！》
I love cabaret!
君達の父って　あの住職！？
Your father is that monk?!
「あの」って　何よ
娘ですが　何か？
What do you mean, "that"?
He is. Any problem?
母親似！？
They must look like their mom.
まあ　つーわけだから
何か　依頼があるなら聞くぞ
So, if you have a request, tell me.
別に
アンタに話すことなんか　ないわ
Don't have one.
There's nothing worth telling you.
（ノワール）ニャー　ニャー
聞こえねえって
Huh? I can't hear you.
（ノワール）ニャー　ニャニャニャー
めんどくせーな…
What a pain in the ass.
Fine.
This is pretty boring.
地味な絵面ね
うん　予想以上に
Yeah, more than I expected.
And Tama was really hopeless.
それで　タマのヤツ
どーしようもなくて
I was there first, but he didn't show any respect.
アタシの方が先輩なのに
礼儀を知らないのよ
That really upset me.
ホント　あったまきちゃう
She said there was nothing to talk about,
I hated how ignorant he was, with his stupid face.
〈話すことないって
言ってたくせに　グチすげえ〉
but now she's going on and on.
バカっ面
誰が　バカっ面ですかい　ノワールこそ
Whose stupid face?!
You should act cuter yourself!
もっと　かわいげを見せたら？
Master, you tell her too!
ダンナからも言ってやってくだせい
Huh? Me?
はあ　俺？
ごめんなさい
Excuse me!
It's not just your face.
バカっ面じゃなくて
バカだったわね
You're an idiot through and through.
You tell him too!
そこのアンタも
言ってやれば？
What?!
They're both a pain in the ass!
〈めんどくせえな　コイツら！〉
えーい　直接　話せ！
Talk to each other directly!
You used to live together, right?
つーか　一緒に暮らしてたんだろ？
Then be more friendly to each other!
なら
ちったー　友好的になれよ！
What do you know about how I was treated?
（ノワール）アタシの受けた仕打ち
アンタに何が　わかるってのよ
Back when my masters used to live together...
まだ　ご主人様達が一緒だった頃→
アタシは
すごく　かわいがられていたわ→
they were good to me.
ある日　汚くてボロボロのアイツが
寺に　迷い込んできたの→
One day, a dirty and beaten cat, this guy, wandered into the temple.
Being kind-hearted, my master named him Tama and took him in.
優しいご主人は
タマと名づけて　受け入れた→
アタシも　この町に慣れるように
いろいろ　案内してあげたわ→
I showed him around town, so he could get used to it.
But as soon as they found out that Tama was a rare male calico cat...
でも　タマが珍しい三毛猫のオスと
判明した途端に…
He's a male calico!
《三毛猫のオスじゃ！》
The father of the family started caring only about Tama!
≪（ノワール）ご主人…　父の方は
タマばかりを　ヒイキしだした
Tama, you can have the expensive canned cat food.
《タマには　高級猫缶じゃよ》
《（タマ）まっしぐら》
Yay!
Tama, you can have an expensive bed.
《タマには　高級ベッドじゃ》
《（タマ）モナム～》
Yeah...
My cabaret expenses...
《キャバクラ代》
Countless amounts of Tama merchandise
...the boom ended immediately after...
My life was turned upside down!
アタシの日常は
一変したのよ
The monk's to blame in this case.
それは　住職に問題が…
Anyway, he's not favoring one over the other now.
今となっては　ヒイキもねえだろう
仲直りすれば？
Why don't you make up with each other?
With this happy-go-lucky cat? Never!
こんな　お調子猫と　誰が！
アタシはね
I'm glad that we're living apart!
別々に暮らすことになって
今では　せいせいしてるの
Not only that.
それだけじゃないわ
ニャムに入れ込んで→
He fell head over heels for Nyam.
What does he see in that old neutered cat?!
あんな　避妊した年増の
どこが　いいのよ！
ニャ　ニャプシッ
Is she in love with Tama?
〈コイツ
タマに気があるんじゃねえの？〉
Well, if Tama comes and apologizes to me, then I guess I'll forgive him.
まッ　タマが謝ってきたら
仲直りくらい
してやっても　いいけどね
She's so twisted.
〈素直じゃねえなあ
結局　仲直りしてえんじゃねえか〉
She does want to make up with him.
ええ～　何で僕が　アイツに
謝らないと　いけないんでさあ
Why do I have to apologize to her?!
Get a life.
お前も　鈍いヤツだなあ
Don't you see how she feels?
女の気持ちくらい　察してやれよ
You're the last person who should talk like that.
〈ダンナには　言われたかないでさあ〉
Deep down, she wants to be friends with you, just like in the good old days.
要は
昔みたいに　仲よくなりてえって
それが　アイツの本心なんだよ
でも　仲よくって　どうすれば…
But how can we be friends?
I dunno, but just walk around the block together.
わかんねえけど
仲よく一緒に　町内　歩け
And apologize.
そして　詫びろ
ニャ…　はい
Yes.
All right, we're set.
よ～し
それじゃあ　そういうことで
We're going to the convenience store
Hurry up and apologize!
〈とっとと詫びろ…　つーか〉
And...
walk...
〈人の　通れるところを　歩け〉
where a human...
should walk!
Damn cats!
コイツらーッ！
I wonder what Kousaka-kun and that girl were talking about?
〈高坂君と　あの女の子〉
〈何の話を　してたのかなあ〉
〈あッ　この道は→〉
This is the street where we used to walk together.
〈昔よく　２匹で散歩した道〉
〈まだ右も左も　わからないときに〉
Back then, I couldn't tell left from right.
Noir showed me the area.
〈ノワールが案内してくれたっけ〉
I know I'm being stubborn, but...
〈アタシも　意地を張ってるって
わかってるけど…〉
《ニャムねえさんって方に
会ったんでさあ》
I met this cat, Nyam nee-san.
She's really kind.
《とても優しい方ですねい》
Nyam nee-san did...
《ニャムねえさんがですねい
ニャムねえさんに》
Nyam nee-san said...
Nyam nee-san is...
《ニャムねえさんって…》
Grrrrrr...
《イライラ　イライラ》
Dumb Tama!
〈タマのバカ〉
A dog?!
（タマ・ノワール）犬ッ！
Dogs?!
犬～ッ！
Stand back, Noir.
下がってな　ノワール
Tama?!
タマ！？
カアーーッ
ニャーッ　やっぱ怖い！
They're still scary!
Help, Master!
ダンナ　助けて～ッ！
He's playing with his cell phone!
…て　携帯いじってる！
ああ～　猫さん達　ごめんね
I'm sorry, kitties.
こらッ　ダメじゃない
Come on, stop!
水野…
Mizuno!
Kousaka-kun!
高坂君…
お散歩中ですか
You're taking them for a walk?
うん　高坂君も？
Yeah.
You too?
Help, Master!
ダンナ　助けて～→
Master!
ダンナ～！
T-Take your tongues off Tama!
タ　タマに何すんのよ！
ありがとう　ノワール
Thank you, Noir!
ノワールが
そばに　いてくれないと
I'm totally useless without you around!
僕は　ダメなんでさあ
タマ…
Tama...
〈こんなところで　会えるとは〉
It's lucky that I ran into her here.
えっと
この間　楽しかったね
Hey, the other day was a lot of fun.
U-Um...
（２人）あ　あの…→
You go ahead...
どうぞ　あの…
Um...
About the girl you were talking to the other day...
この間　一緒にいた女の子って
女の子？
A girl?
猫地蔵の呪いが
どうこう言ってた…
Something about the "curse of the cat statue."
聞いてた？
聞いちゃった
You heard that?
I overheard it.
〈このままじゃ　水野にも災いが…〉
Misfortune will befall Mizuno too at this rate!
〈ごまかさないと〉
I need to trick her!
The curse of the cat statue...
猫地蔵の呪い…
そうなんだ　のろい　ノロイ
I meant the slowness! Yeah! That's it!
Note: As a noun, noroi means "a curse."  As an adjective or adverb, it means "slow."
猫地蔵　動きがノロくてさ
１年に３ミリしか進まないんだよ
It can only move three millimeters a year!
Even the hair on a Kikuko Doll grows faster, you know?
菊子人形の髪が伸びるスピードより
遅いよな～　ハハハッ
そうだったんだ
Oh, that was it?
〈はあ　ごまかせた〉
Success!
So, who's that girl?
それで　あの女の子って…
えッ？
I know this might sound strange,
You're not strong enough.
犬ぐらいで　だらしないわね
but I was wondering about your relationship with her...
That's why you'll be scum forever.
それだから
いつまでたっても　ダメ男なのよ
Wh-What?!
なッ　何ですってい！
You too. You'd better act cute, or nobody will ever want to marry you.
ノワールの方こそ　もっと
かわいげのある女にならないと
嫁の　もらい手
絶望的ですぜい
Look who's talking!
（ノワール）他人の
心配している暇があって？→
You're just like a girl, always complaining!
オスのくせに
グチグチと　女々しいのよ！
I can't hear her...
〈聞こえねえ！〉
For the upcoming school trip—
Jeez, shut up already.
〈うるせえな　少し黙ってろよ〉
I'm trying to talk with Mizuno!
〈水野と話してんだから〉
That's why even Nyam doesn't like you much.
Um, um, Kousaka-kun, what kind of—
だから　ニャムにも
相手にされないのね　かわいそう
Poor boy!
ノワーーール！
Noir!
Tama!
タマーーッ！
黙れーッ！
Shut the hell up!
みッ　水野　今のは…
M-Mizuno, that was...
I'm so sorry!
ごめんなさ～い
うわ～　やっぱり～ッ
I knew it!
Senpai!
せんぱーい　終わった？
Are you done?
うん…　終わった
Yeah, I'm done for.
（朱莉）アイス　食べる？
Want some ice cream?
…うん
Yeah.
I'm sorry!
すみませんでした
まあ→
Well,
I enjoyed the walk a little.
少しは　楽しめたわ…　散歩
あらッ？
Oh?
あら～　幸せそうねえ
Oh my, they look happy.
≪（加奈子）ああッ　気になる！→
It's bothering me!
I need to ask Junpei directly, or it'll keep bothering me!
やっぱ潤平に　直接　聞かないと
モヤモヤする！
What's this "twin-tail" deal?
何なんだよ　ツインテールって
あッ？
ワン　ワン
Kaede! What's the matter?
楓　どうしたんだ？
何でもないの　何でも…
It's nothing. Really.
何でもないこと　ないだろう！
It doesn't look like nothing.
≪（加奈子）楓！
Kaede!
Well, Kousaka-kun was...
あのね　高坂君が…
Oh, tickets to an art museum?
≪（爺）ほう　美術館のチケットですか
（凪）高坂に　やろうと思ってね→
I want to give one to Kousaka.
美しいものを見れば
心も美しくなれる→
Looking at beauty will make his heart beautiful too.
楓に　ふさわしい男に
なってもらわねば
He must become a man suitable for Kaede!
Yes.
（爺）はい　ところで
このあたりのはずですが
Anyway, it should be around here.
Excuse us.
ちょっと　よろしいですか？
はい
Yes?
この辺に　高坂というお宅が
高坂…
I'm looking for a Kousaka family that lives in this area.
Kousaka?
ああ　潤平君なら
If you're after Junpei-kun, he's in the park with two twin-tailed girls.
公園で　ツインテールの女の子と
一緒だったわよ
Twin...
I guess he was too forceful with her the other day and made her cry, but I can't blame him.
この前は　道端で　強引に迫って
泣かせちゃったみたいだけど
仕方ないわよね
女体に興味がある　お年頃だし→
He's at the age where he's interested in girls.
仲直りして　よかったわ　それじゃ
I'm glad they made up.
Well then...
テール…
Tails...
ほっぺたに　ついてるわよ
You've got some on your cheek.
≪（加奈子）潤平～ッ！
≪（凪）高坂～ッ！
Junpei!
Kousaka!
先輩に　何すんのよ！
Hey! What are you doing to Senpai?!
あららら…
ステキ～
Oh my, oh my...
This is wonderful.
どなったのは
水野の声が　聞こえなかったから
I yelled at the cats because I couldn't hear Mizuno.
猫に対して　言ったのであって…
So that's what it was.
そうだったんだ
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい　ビックリしちゃって
It surprised me.
ビックリさせて　ごめん
I'm sorry I surprised you.
そういや～　あの２人は？
Where did those two go?
おお～　何て美しいシンメトリー→
What beautiful sisters!
Let me take care of you, my dears!
さあ　お姉さんが
かわいがってあげよう
No, thank you.
いや　結構です
危ない人…
She's suspicious
They're the daughters of the monk at my neighborhood temple.
昇福寺の住職の娘で
ご近所さんの…
単なる　後輩です
They're our kouhai.
そっかあ
I see!
I hope things don't become even more complicated.
〈ややこしいことに
なんなきゃ　いいけどな…〉
Oh, my God!
（凪）オー　マイ　ゴー
パイナップ～ル
Pineapple!
You shall be my dessert for tonight!
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru anata no sugata
I see you chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu!
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow!
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
Strawberry Tears
Strawberry tears.
Today's Nyan Koma.
Today's Mew view
なあ　ところで
退魔って　何？
Hey, what's this "warding"?
ゲーム　あんま　やんねえし
わかんねえんだけど
I don't play games all that much, so I don't get it.
（くまねこ）僕は　こう思うのね
This is my guess.
Taima Fighters Shofuku Five!
タイマ　レッド
タイマ　ブルー
Taima Red!
Taima Blue!
タイマ　ホワイト
タイマ　ブラック
Taima White!
Taima Black!
タイマ　ブラック　その２
Taima Black #2!
（メカ猫地蔵）ギャース
≪（朱莉）今日こそ　決着よ
メカ猫地蔵！
We'll end this once and for all, Mecha Cat Statue!
≪（琴音）あッ　もう時間が…
Oh, time's up.
…て　そりゃ　タイマー
That's a timer!
Anyway, the next Nyan Koi...
Master, I heard that you'll be traveling to Kyoto?
Then please take Masa-nii with you.
Let me visit my home with you.
A four-day school trip starts today!
I'm completely free!
Or I was supposed to be...
Hey, Junpei!
Do you wanna hang around with us?
More people means more fun.
Right, Kaede?
Y-Yeah, let's go, Kousaka-kun.
Next Nyan Koi, 7th nyan-ko, "Please Wait Until Dark♡"
Awright!
I'll use this chance to get closer to Mizuno!